♪♪～
（アラジン）アリババ…　くん？
Ali... baba?
♪♪～
（カシム）知り合いなのか？
（アリババ）ああ。
Friend of yours?
Yeah.
アラジン　久しぶりだな。
Aladdin, it's been a while!
ウーゴくんをしまってくれないか？
俺の仲間が　ビビってる。
Do you think you could recall Ugo for me?
He's scaring my friends.
（ジャーファル）
ダメだ！　言うことを聞くな！
Don't do it!
Don't listen to him!
♪♪～
あのね　アリババくん→
Hey, Alibaba.
I came out here so that I could see you again.
僕　アリババくんに
会いに来たんだよ。
I have so much to tell you!
話したいことが
たくさん　あるんだよ。
あのときのことを
覚えているだろう？
Don't you remember our promise?
We said we'd see the world together!
一緒に　世界を見に行こうって
約束したもんね。
♪♪～
Aladdin.
アラジン　ごめん…。
I'm sorry.
約束は　守れなくなったんだ。
I can't keep that promise.
（兵士）いたぞ！
（兵士）待て　こらぁ！
The army's here!
（ザイナブ）国軍が来たぞ！
Alibaba, we've gotta get out of here!
（カシム）おい　アリババ　ずらかるぞ！
ああ。
Got it.
♪♪～
厳格と礼節の精霊よ→
Spirit of propriety and discipline,
汝と　汝の眷属に命ず。
I command thee and thine.
我が魔力を糧として→
With my magoi as your source,
我が意志に　大いなる力を与えよ。
use your great power to bring my will to life!
Come forth, Amon!
出でよ　アモン。
♪♪～
うわぁ～！
ほ…　炎の魔人だ。
H-He's a fire demon!
ふん！
♪♪～
akogare wo ima tsukanda
My desires are within reach.
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
♪♪～
ashita kara umare kawaru toka
People say they'll change the next day.
dareka ga mikiri tsuketa toka
But they give up so easily.
kono machi no style toka
That's just how it is here.
sonna mono ni nagasare tsuzukete
They get swept away by those excuses day by day.
kado no toreta genseki ni ha
They're nothing more than a chip, swept off the edge
kitto daremo you ha nai
and no longer needed by anyone.
♪♪～
fushigi to tobira no mukou ni ha
Guess what? Out there,
v.i.p nanoru yatsu ha naku
no one's swaggering around like a VIP.
daremo ga kunou no hate sa ore mo
Everyone suffers their own heartaches, myself included.
akogare wo ima tsukanda
But my desires are within reach.
♪♪～
mi wo yudanereba ii  kaji ha kono te ni
Throw yourself in with abandon. I've got the wheel.
mitsu kazoete the show time
On the count of three, it's show time!
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
♪♪～
8th Night
A Broken Promise
（シンドバッド）それにしても　霧の団に→
That's unexpected.
There's a dungeon capturer in the Fog Troupe?
迷宮攻略者がいるとはな。→
And he's the person Aladdin's been looking for?
しかも
それが　アラジンの友人とは。→
Just what kind of person is this Miracle Man Alibaba?
怪傑アリババとは
どういうヤツなんだ？
♪♪～
These guys are scary!
（Ｌナンド）にいちゃん
この人たち　怖いよ…。　大丈夫？
You sure about this?
（Ｓナンド）ああ。　ここなら
国軍も　手を出せないからな。→
Yeah.
The army can't get us here.
俺たちは　安泰だ。
We couldn't be safer.
Perfect timing.
ちょうど今
仲間を集めているところだ。
We were just looking for some new allies.
If you've got nowhere else to be, you're welcome here.
行くとこがねぇなら　歓迎するぜ。
なあ？　相棒。
Right, partner?
Yeah.
ああ。
だが　これだけは言っておく。
But listen up.
俺たちは　義賊だ。
We're chivalrous thieves.
We fight against the army for the sake of the slums.
スラムのために国軍と戦っている。
Don't you even think about stealing for your own dirty purposes.
盗賊気分で　汚ぇ盗みはするな。
もし　この掟を破ったら…。
If you do...
（３人）ひぃ…。
命で償ってもらう。
You'll pay for it with your lives.
なあ　カシム
お前　どういうつもりだよ？
Kassim!
What was that all about?
Why are you taking in so many unknown men?
あんな得体の知れねぇヤツらを
どんどん引き込んで。
Wanna start a war?
ひとつ　戦争でも　おっぱじめるか。
おい！
冗談　冗談。
What?
Just kidding.
だが　俺たちは
戦い続けなきゃなんねぇ。
But the truth is we have no choice but to keep fighting.
はははっ！　アリババにいちゃん！
Alibaba!
今日も　国軍やっつけた？
にいちゃんのおかげで→
Did you beat the army today too?
We get to eat twice a day now thanks to you!
みんな　一日２回も
飯を食えるようになったんだよ。
あっ…。
なあ　相棒→
Hey partner.
俺たちもガキの頃　スラムの地獄を→
When we were kids, we struggled through life together down in the slums. Remember?
一緒に　生き抜いたよな。→
Please save these kids.
頼む…
この子供たちを救ってくれ。→
マリアムみたいにしないでくれ。
Don't let them end up like Mariam.
Please don't leave us, Alibaba!
もう　どこへも行かないでくれ
アリババ！→
Fight by my side, just like when we were kids!
俺のそばで
昔みたいに戦ってくれ。
（心の声）≪ダメだ。
一人で　なんとかするって→
No!
I resolved to take care of this myself!
決めたじゃねぇか≫
はっ…　誰だ!?
Who's there?
Just my imagination...
気のせいか。
だいぶ疲れてるのかもな。
I must be more exhausted than I thought.
うわぁ～…　んんっ！
（モルジアナ）静かにしてください。
Please keep quiet.
騒ぐと落とします。
んん～…　んんっ！
Or I will silence you.
どうして　ここに？
あなたの匂いを　たどってきました。
Why are you here?
I tracked your scent here.
なぜ　盗賊など
やっているんですか？
Why are you with the thieves?
Please explain yourself to Aladdin.
訳を　アラジンに　話してください。
There's nothing to explain.
話すことなんて　何もねぇよ。
Also, you're in a den of thieves.
それより　ここは　盗賊の巣だぞ。
Leave before you get yourself killed.
殺されねぇうちに　帰るんだな。
いいえ　帰りません。
I will not.
アラジンは　あなたに会うために→
Aladdin traveled for a long, long time to get here and see you.
長い長い道のりを
旅してきたのです。
And what of it?
それが　どうした？
あなただって　半年前は
チーシャンの町で　アラジンを→
Were you not also searching for
Aladdin just half a year ago in Qishan?
捜していたではありませんか。
うるせぇ！
Shut up!
お前にゃ　関係ねぇことだろ。
これは　俺の問題だ。
This has nothing to do with you!
This is my problem!
ドスン！
うわっ！
It does have to do with me.
関係なくありません。
えっ？
ええっ？
あなたを　アラジンのもとへ→
I will take you to Aladdin now.
連れていきます。
ええ～～っ!?
Nooo!
い～～やぁ～～～!!
（Ｌナンド）
ん？　悲鳴が聞こえなかった？
Did you just hear someone scream?
（Ｓナンド）気のせいだろ。
（Ｍナンド）にしても　兄上→
You're hearing things.
Anyway, Brother.
As long as we sell these,
霧の団に入らなくても
これを売れば→
we'll have a roof over our heads and enough money to fool around even if we don't join the Fog Troupe.
当分は　遊んで暮らせるのに。
I only trust gold and silver.
（Ｓナンド）
俺は　金貨　銀貨しか信じねぇ。
If we sold this stuff in Balbadd now, we'd get nothing but these scraps of paper.
こいつを
今のバルバッドで売っても→
こんな紙切れにしか
ならねぇからな。
Red: Kou Empire.   Black: 1.
Balbadd's economy is currently in a terrible state of disorder.
（ジャーファル）バルバッドの経済は今
激しく混乱しています。
その原因の一つが　これです。
And this is one of the reasons.
Black: 10,000.   Red: Kou Empire.
Paper money issued by the Kou Empire.
（シンドバッド）
煌帝国の発行する煌紙幣か。
The Kou Empire is using their military prowess
（ジャーファル）
煌帝国は　軍事力に物を言わせて→
to try to circulate this paper money even in neighboring countries.
近隣諸国にまで　この煌紙幣を→
流通させようとしています。→
Balbadd's king, Ahbmad, has fallen under their influence.
バルバッド国王アブマドも
煌帝国の言いなりです。→
According to my research, it appears that he has married a princess of the Kou Empire.
調べたところ
どうやら　煌帝国の皇女と→
婚約しているらしく。
（シンドバッド）なんだと？
He's what?
あの野郎
なんで　俺に言わねぇんだよ。
That jerk.
He didn't tell me that.
There's also the problem of the Fog Troupe.
霧の団の問題もありますし
こちらも　出方を考えて→
Perhaps we should think about our next move and get in touch with our home country.
本国に　連絡を取った方が
いいかもしれません。
Yeah, you're right.
そうだな。　俺　金属器ねぇし。
I have no metal vessels on me, after all.
Speaking of that, where's Aladdin?
そういえば　アラジンは？
He was rather depressed and is now resting in his room.
（ジャーファル）気落ちしてしまって
部屋で　休んでいます。→
マギといっても
普通の子供なんですね。
He may be a Magi, but he's still just a child.
この半年間で
僕たちに　いろいろあったように→
A lot has happened to us in this past year.
アリババくんにも
きっと　いろいろあったんだよね。
I'm sure a lot has happened to Alibaba as well.
What should we do now?
さあ　これから　どうしようかな。
新しい目標を立てなきゃね。
We need to come up with a new plan!
ウーゴくんに頼まれていた
金属器集めの続きをしようか…。
Should we continue our quest to collect the metal vessels, like you asked me too?
あっ　その前に　モルさんと一緒に→
But before that, maybe we should go with Mor to see the Dark Continent?
暗黒大陸に行ってみるのもいいな。
I want to learn a lot from Mister Sinbad too!
シンドバッドのおじさんにも
いろいろ教えてもらいたいし→
やることが　いっぱいだよ！
There's so much to do!
あれ？
Huh?
なんか…　力が入らないや…。
I... don't seem to have any strength.
楽しみに…　してたんだけどな。
I was... so excited too.
うわぁ～～!!
≪ドーン！
あっ。
がっ…。
よ…　よう…。
H-Hey.
♪♪～
げ…　元気そうだな。
Y-You look well.
Yeah. You too.
うん　アリババくんも。
半年ぶりだなぁ。
It's been half a year, huh?
お前　ちょっと
感じ変わったんじゃねぇか？
You've changed!
うん　アリババくんも。
Yeah... You too...
♪♪～
Please cut the small talk.
本題に入ってください。
うっ…。
あなたの霧の団のせいで→
Do you know what's happening to this country because of your Fog Troupe?
今　この国で
何が起きているか知っていますか？
Domestic insurrections have caused trade to come to a halt,
内乱で　交易が止まり
政府が　市民を見放し→
the government is abandoning its citizens,
逃げ出した
罪もない貧しい人たちが→
and formerly free, innocent people, whose only crime is poverty,
are being forced into slavery.
奴隷狩りされているんですよ。
まあまあ　モルさん。
Mor, don't be like that.
With everything going on, I understand your anger,
いろいろあって
怒るのも分かるけどさ→
but it's been so long since the three of us have been together.
せっかく　三人で
久しぶりに会えたんだし…→
そういえば　いい月夜だし→
It's a beautiful night.
みんなで
もっと楽しい話をしようよ。
Let's talk about happier things.
ねっ　アリババくん。
Right, Alibaba?
Oh...
あっ…。　おう。
Yeah.
Wow, you did all that?
へえ～　そんなことがあったのか。
Sounds like a great adventure.
そりゃあ　大冒険だったな。
うん。　そして→
Yeah.
And now, I'm to capture the Fog Troupe.
僕は　この国で　霧の団を→
捕まえることになったんだ。
I didn't know you'd be with them though.
そこに　君がいるとは
思わなかったけど…。
でも　なんの理由もなく
君が　そんなことをするとは→
I'm sure you have a reason for what you're doing.
思えないんだ。
教えてよ　君が　霧の団にいる訳を。
Please tell me why.
To do that, first I need to tell you my friend's story. Is that okay?
アラジン　先に→
俺の友達の話を　聞いてくれるか？
うん　いいよ。
Yeah, of course.
My friend's name is Kassim.
そいつは　カシムっていうんだ。
カシム？
Kassim?
ああ。　霧の団の本当のリーダーさ。
Yeah.
He's the real leader of the Fog Troupe.
Kassim was my friend during my childhood days.
カシムは
俺の昔からの友達だったんだ。
（カシム・回想）((くっ！))
((はははっ！))
I got it!
（カシム）((取ったぞ！
俺が　この山のボスだ！))
I'm the king of the mountain!
((ちくしょ～！))
((さすが　カシム！　すげぇ))
Yeah!
Go Kassim!
Yeah, I knew no one could beat me!
（カシム）((やっぱ
俺に　かなうヤツはいねぇな。→
あっ！))
((へっへ～！))
((油断してちゃいけねぇよ
カシムくん))
Don't let your guard down, Kassim!
I dug tons of tunnels under this mountain.
((なぜなら
この山には　俺が掘った→
無数のトンネルがあるんだ))
((名付けて　トンネル殺法！))
（カシム）((なっ!?))
I call it my Killer Tunnel Plan!
What?
((アリババ　すげぇ～！))
((でも　せこい！))
Wow Alibaba, you're awesome!
Kinda a cheater too!
（カシム）((てめぇ
生意気なんだよ　アリババ！))
You brat!
((生意気って言う方が
生意気なんだよ！))
The real brat is the only who calls others a brat!
((なんだと!?　こんにゃろ～め！))
((うわっ！))
What was that? Why you little!
We were always fighting,
しょっちゅう　ケンカしてたけど→
俺たちは　不思議と　ウマが合った。
but strangely enough, we were still friends.
ゴミ溜めの街を
毎日　一緒に走り回った。
We ran around the garbage-filled streets together everyday.
生活は　貧しかったけど→
Life was hard, but I had a caring mother at home.
家に帰れば
優しい　おふくろがいた。
((ただいま　母ちゃん))
I'm home, Mom!
Mother was a prostitute in the slums.
おふくろは　スラム街の娼婦だった。
明るい人でさ。
俺は　いつも幸せだった。
She was always laughing and we were happy together.
だけど　カシムは違った。
But it was different for Kassim.
His father was a good-for-nothing loser.
あいつの父親は
ろくでもない男だった。
((このクソガキ！))
((うっ！　ううっ…))
You filthy brat!
（マリアム）((うわぁ～…))
((酒　買ってこいっつっただろ！))
I told you to get off your lazy ass and bring me some alcohol!
((うるせぇ！　てめぇも
ビービーわめくんじゃねぇ！))
Shut up!
Stop your crying!
((あっ！　やめろ！
マリアムに　手を出すな！→
Stop!
Don't hit Mariam!
あっ！))
（マリアム）((お兄ちゃん…))
Kassim!
((ふん！　兄妹そろって→
Hmph! Worthless, the both of you!
クソの役にも立ちゃしねぇ))
((ちっ…))
そんなある日　カシムの父親が
スラムから消えた。
One day, Kassim's father disappeared from the slums.
まあ　スラムじゃ　よくある話だ。
That happened frequently down in the slums.
おふくろは　そんな
カシムとマリアムを引き取った。
Mother took in both Kassim and Mariam,
and the four of us became a family.
そうして
俺たち四人は　家族になったんだ。
家族か。　にぎやかそうでいいね。
A family!
Sounds really exciting.
ああ。　にぎやかで　楽しかったよ。
Yeah, it was always loud, lively, and fun.
だけど　そんな生活も
長くは　続かなかった。
But that didn't last for long.
おふくろが
病気で死んじまったんだ。
Before long, my mother died of an illness.
俺は　泣くことしかできなかった。
I couldn't do anything but cry.
だけど　カシムは違った。
But Kassim was different.
((泣くな。　これからは→
Don't cry.
From now on, I'll protect us.
俺が　お前らを守ってやる))
俺たちは　ガキ同士
力を合わせて　本当に頑張ったよ。
We worked together, the three of us kids, and we tried really hard.
ゴミ拾いに　靴磨き→
We scavenged through the trash, we shined shoes, and we gave tours.
それに　観光案内。
だけど　やがて　カシムは→
But before long, Kassim fell in with a bad group of kids and turned to thievery.
街の悪ガキどもとつるんで
盗みをするようになった。
カシムも　生活を守るのに
必死だったのかもしれない。
He was probably pretty desperate to make sure we all survived.
だから　ある日　俺は言ったんだ。
That's why, one day, I asked him.
((カシム　俺も手伝おうか？))
Kassim, should I help too?
((お前が
そんなことする必要はねぇ))
You don't need to dirty your hands.
((お前は　俺なんかと違うからな))
You're not like me.
((な…　なんだよ　それ))
W-What's that mean?
（カシム）((俺は　あのおやじの
血を引いてる根っからの悪党だ。→
I share the same blood as that loser of a father. I'm rotten by nature.
でも　お前は違う。→
But you're not.
お前は　お前の母さんみたいに
まっとうに生きてくれ))
You should live a respectable life, just like your mom did.
((カシム…))
But Kassim!
あの日のカシムは
少し　おかしかった。
Kassim acted kind of strange that day.
（カシム）((なあ　俺ら　友達だよな？))
Hey, we're friends right?
((おう！　当ったり前だろ))
((ははっ…))
Yeah!
Of course!
That day, the king of Balbadd came down to the slums.
そんなある日　バルバッドの国王が
スラムにやってきた。
（先代国王）((お前は私の息子だ。→
You're my son.
これから　王宮で暮らすのだ))
You are to come and live at the palace.
((はっ？　そんなわけないだろ))
What?
No way!
My mother was a prostitute.
((おふくろは娼婦で　俺は
誰の子かも分かんないんだぞ))
I have no idea who my father is!
（先代国王）
((お前の母親アニスは→
Your mother, Anise, was once a maid at the royal palace.
昔　王宮に仕える下女だった。→
そこで　私は　彼女を見初めた。→
That is where I met her and fell in love with her at first sight.
And that is where you come from.
そして　お前が生まれたのだ))
（カシム）((やっぱりな。
前から　不思議だったんだよ→
I knew it.
I always thought it was weird.
なんで　お前みたいなヤツが
ここにいるんだって))
Why was someone like you here in this dump?
((ど…　どういう意味だよ？))
W-What do you mean?
I don't mean anything.
（カシム）
((どういう意味も　クソもねぇよ))
The two of us are different. We have been since birth.
((お前と俺とは
生まれながらにして→
違う人間なんだ。
とっとと　どこへでも行っちまえ))
Get out of here.
((えっ？　くっ！))
カシムなら
引き止めてくれると思った。
I thought Kassim would stop me.
He... was my family!
だって　カシムは　家族だったから。
なのに…。
But...
結局
そのまま俺は　スラムを後にした。
In the end, I left the slums.
((でっかい))
((こちらです　王子様))
It's huge...
This way please, my prince.
((お…　王子様？))
P-Prince?
♪♪～
俺の暮らしは　一変した。
My life was turned upside down.
身の回りの世話は
すべて　下女がやってくれ→
I had maids to attend to my every need.
話し方や歩き方→
I was put through harsh lessons everyday.
学問　剣術に至るまで→
They ranged from the way I spoke and the way I walked,
毎日　厳しい訓練が課せられた。
to my studies and my swordplay.
And just like that, three years time went by.
そして　３年の月日が流れ→
My days in the slums had faded into a distant memory.
スラムでの日々が
遠い記憶になっていったんだ。
♪♪～
ある日　スラムを
ひと目見たくなった俺は→
One day, I felt a desire to see the slums once again and secretly snuck out of the palace.
こっそり　王宮を抜け出した。
But there was nothing there.
でも　そこには　何もなかった。
The garbage-filled streets were clean and remodeled,
ゴミ溜めの街は
きれいに整備され→
but not a single person from the slums was to be found.
スラムの住人は
一人もいなかった。
♪♪～
((あっ！))
なんで　あのとき
カシムに会っちまったんだろう。
Why did I have to run into him then?
あのとき
俺が　王宮を抜け出さなければ→
If only I hadn't snuck out of the palace that night!
あんな事件は起こらなかったんだ。
Then nothing would've happened.
What happened?
あんな事件？
Kassim?
((カシム…。　カ…　カシムだろ？))
You're Kassim, aren't you?
I haven't seen you in forever!
((久しぶりだな))
((よう！　アリババじゃないか。
久しぶりだなぁ。→
Hey!
If it isn't Alibaba!
It's really been forever!
はははっ！))
((あっ))
（カシム）((再会に！))
Cheers to our reunion!
((カシム　今　何してんだよ？))
Kassim, what are you up to now?
Where's Mariam and everyone else from the slums?
((マリアムや
スラムのみんなは　どこへ？))
（カシム）((みんな　無事さ。
だが　スラムは　もうねぇ))
They're all fine.
But the slums are no more.
((国に　追い出されたんだよ))
The country drove us out.
((再開発が　どうのこうのって…))
Said a bunch of garbage about redevelopment.
((お前　なんも知らねぇのな))
You really don't know anything, do you?
((俺　ほとんど
王宮に　閉じ込められてるから))
I've pretty much been locked in the palace the whole time.
((まっ　今日は　そんなしけた話は
いいじゃねぇか))
Let's leave those gloomy topics for another time.
((飲もうぜ。→
Drink up!
What's wrong?
あれ？
ひと口も飲んでねぇじゃねぇか))
You haven't even taken a sip!
((もしかして　飲めねぇの？))
((の…　飲めるよ！))
Could it be that you can't drink?
I-I can too!
♪♪～
((おお～　おっ。
ははっ！　いい飲みっぷり))
Wow, that was impressive!
俺たちは
あっという間に　昔に戻った。
And just like that, we were back to three years ago.
でも　今　思い返すと気付くんだ→
I didn't see it then,
あいつが
一瞬　暗い目をしていたことに。
but looking back on it now, I remember
how his eyes darkened for just a second.
カシムは　あの日→
Kassim had made a decision that day, from the moment he saw me.
俺と出会ったときから
決意していたんだ…→
あの事件を起こすことを。
A decision that would bring about disaster.
Oh yeah, you said you were locked in the palace, didn't you?
（カシム）((そういや　さっき
王宮に　閉じ込められてるって→
言ってたよな？　じゃあ
どうやって　ここまで来たんだ？))
Then how'd you get out here?
((ふっふっふっふ～！))
((それはな～　トンネルさ))
Through the tunnels!
（カシム）((トンネル？))
((覚えてるだろ？))
Tunnels?
You remember how I was the master of tunneling?
((俺が　トンネル作りの
名人だったってことをよ))
((へえ～…))
Oh?
♪♪～
Hey Kassim, you remember how I
punched you on the day I left for the palace?
((なあ　カシム…
俺が　王宮に入る日さ→
I'm sorry about that.
その…　殴って悪かったな))
When you said to get out of there...
((でも
どこへでも行けって言ったけど→
あれ…　あれ→
You... You were trying to look out for me, right?
俺のために
言ってくれたんだろ？))
((ああ。　当然じゃねぇか))
Of course!
We're best friends, aren't we?
((俺たち親友だろ？))
((あっ))
俺は　うれしかった。
I was so happy.
カシムが　俺のためを
思っていてくれたことを。
Kassim just wanted the best for me.
((ははっ))
だから　気付かなかったんだ→
That's why I didn't realize
あいつの部下に
つけられていたことに。
that he had his guys follow me back.
ほんと　バカだよな～　俺…。
I'm such an idiot.
アリババくん…。
Alibaba...
それから　しばらくたったある日→
A little while after that,
俺は　病床の国王に呼ばれた。
I was called to the bedside of the ailing king.
I don't have much longer.
（先代国王）
((わしは　もう長くない。→
アブマドは　怠け者で
他国の言いなりだ。→
Ahbmad is lazy and quick to fall under the influence of other nations.
Alibaba, I want to leave this country to you.
アリババ
この国を　お前に任せたい))
((えっ？　私には　そんな…))
To me? I couldn't...
（先代国王）
((だが　お前に頼むしかない))
I have no one to turn to but you.
((陛下　一つだけ
お聞きしたいことがあります))
Your Majesty, there is one thing I would like to ask.
（先代国王）((なんだ？))
((陛下は　母さん…→
What is it?
How did you feel about Mom... er, my mother?
いえ　私の母のことを
どう思っていましたか？))
（先代国王）((アニス…。
たくさんの　しがらみがあって→
Anise?
We couldn't be together...
一緒には　なれなかったなぁ…。→
We had too many obligations.
しかし…　うん→
But...
愛していたよ))
I loved her.
♪♪～
((陛下　ありがとうございます))
Thank you, Your Majesty.
((そのお言葉があれば
私は　ここで　やっていけます))
With that knowledge, I know I can make it here.
♪♪～
((≪うわっ！))
((あっ))
((私が　見てきましょう))
((アリババ))
I will go see what is happening.
Alibaba.
♪♪～
((大丈夫です。　陛下は　ここに))
Don't worry.
Please wait here, Your Majesty.
身の引き締まる思いだった。
My body still tenses at the memory.
((あっ…　カシム))
Kassim?
((あっ？))
((バシ！))
((うっ！))
What should we do with him, chief?
((どうします？　お頭))
（カシム）((ああ…))
Hm...
((カシム…))
Kassim...
((殺すこたぁねぇ。
縛って　放っておけ))
Don't kill him.
Tie him up and leave him.
♪♪～
そうさ…　カシムが
財宝を盗み出すのに　使ったのは→
Kassim used the tunnels that I had told him about
that one night to steal the treasures from the palace.
俺が
店で話したトンネルだったんだ。
♪♪～
（ハッサン）
カシム　アリババが拉致られた。
Kassim, Alibaba's been kidnapped!
団員を集めろ。　奪還だ。
Gather the men.
We'll get him back.
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
me ni mieru sekai ha subete kako no monogatari sa
The world you see before your eyes is a story already told.
♪♪～
kagayaku mirai wo miushinau na yo
Don't lose sight of the bright future ahead.
♪♪～
kimi ni ha motto ippai yume to kibou ga arun da
You're destined to realize great hopes and dreams.
bootto shitetara minogashichau zo
But if you blink for too long, they'll leave you behind.
♪♪～
dekinai riyuu sagasu yori
Instead of searching for an excuse,
♪♪～
yatte mireba ii
why not just give it a try?
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
yubi to yubi wo marume ryoume ni ate
Make circles with your fingers and put them around your eyes.
imeeji shite sagashiteru mono
Picture your hopes and dreams!
♪♪～
atama no naka no adobenchaaa
Picture your personal adventure story!
doko he mukau?
Where are you headed?
yubi bouenkyou
What can you see
♪♪～
yubi no sono sukima ni nani ga mieru?
in the space between your fingers?
tooi you demo hontou ha chikai
It might seem far, but it's really not.
yogen no you na takaramono
It's a promise as valuable as any treasure!
Let's settle this leader to leader, Miracle Man Alibaba.
That's rather harsh.
The traitor's fate is but the gallows.
Next time: A Prince's Duty.
9th Night
A Prince's Duty
Think about it, brother!
Our people are suffering and dying!
（シンドバッド）大将同士
決着を　つけようじゃないか→
怪傑アリババ君。
（ジャーファル）厳しいですが→
反逆者の末路は　処刑台です。
考えてくれ　兄さん！
国民は　死ぬほど苦しんでるんだ！
３連休最終日の今日、
各地の高速道路は行楽地などから
戻る車で
混雑していて、ところによって
５０ｋｍ以上の激しい渋滞となっ
ている。